YUYOU YU

104 Royce Road, Manchester, M15 5LA $(+44)07800900077 \diamond y.y.yu@outlook.com$

I started my programming journey by writing small Python script for work and fun. Meanwhile, I built the knowledge of front end HTML and CSS. I found that I was fascinated by programming and started to learn some backend technology and C by myself. There were some difficulties in the learning process so I joined Northcoders' coding bootcamp to start learning systematically. Although I have only been trained as a software engineer for less than four months, I have had a good understanding and practice of frontend, backend, data base and network.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Language JavaScript, C, Python

Frontend React, Material-UI, HTML, CSS

Backend Express, PostgreSQL

Testing Jest, Selenium

Other React Native, Git, Vim

EXPERIENCE

Northcoders, Manchester

09/2020 - 01/2021

Trainee Software Developer

- · Trained to be a professional software developer in Northcoders' 14 weeks coding bootcamp.
- · Built experiences to work in pairs and groups remotely.

Xinlung Group Ltd, Manchester

09/2019 - 06/2020

 $Accommodation \ advisor$

- · Self-learned Python to improve work efficiency:
 - Used Python script to download structured data from multiple web pages and converting into Excel format;
- Used Python-Wechat API to send notification messages to certain students automatically.
- · Helped students to find the most suitable accommodation based on individual needs. Provided high level of customer service while achieving the sales targets. Received zero complain. Helped the company to build positive reputation.
- · Built and executed two email marketing campaigns to raise students' awareness on products and sales events(e.g. live stream). 23% of the students booked accommodation with us afterwards.

EDUCATION

the University of Manchester

BSc. Fashion Marketing

2016 - 2019

- Achieved 2-2 honor degree
- Worked as financial manager in the final year project of starting a business.
- Grasp multiple software including InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and Microsoft Office.

the University of Manchester

BSc. Management

2015 - 2016

New College Durham

BTEC Level 3

2013 - 2015

• Achieved triple grade Distinction* Distinction* Distinction

• English: C, Maths: A*, Additional Maths: B

SKILLS

Language Mandarin(Native), English(fluent)

Software & Tools MS Office, Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Pottery, Board games, Hiking